<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Articles</title>
    <link>/tags/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 20:50:36 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Articles Contribution (Pt. 2 Howto)</title>
      <link>/post/howto-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 20:50:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/howto-content/</guid>
      <description>Content creators, get ready The gory details We are using Netlify CMS here.
For those wants to hack with this Netlify CMS.
It is a static site powered by Hugo hosted on Netlify.
The posts are hosted at the git repo&amp;rsquo;s site/content directory.
Opinions are welcomed.
How to publish For those who adapt with Markdown and Git, you can submit a pull request to the article repo https://github.com/engineersmy/articles.
You can also login to the admin dashboard via your Github account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Articles Contribution (Pt. 1 Content)</title>
      <link>/post/content-we-want/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 20:01:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/content-we-want/</guid>
      <description>We need articles, what are we looking for? Content contributors we&amp;rsquo;re looking for  One off article Series (weekly, monthly&amp;hellip;) about a certain topic Cross posting (we&amp;rsquo;re glad to mirror posts with proper attribution)  We&amp;rsquo;re looking for the following contents Technical  Tutorial Guide Snippets with explanation Technical user group introduction Project introduction  Non Technical  News, especially about the industry Business related (tips and tricks or experience sharing)  As of now, we don&amp;rsquo;t have much guidelines yet, but posts will be moderated</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, World!</title>
      <link>/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 20:43:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello, World! But it doesn&amp;rsquo;t stop here. Engineers.My is a public working group, aims to build an open source platform for learning, sharing and collaboration.
The current goals  Cross pollination and collaboration between different technical groups Advertise local open source projects Curation of local tech news and meetups Technical articles Newsletter  What this movement is not about  To replace technical groups Yet another chat room Not a meetup group, not the priority for now  What we need help for  Homepage design Article contribution Design works  Details will be coming soon, for now, ping the folks on Slack for more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>